<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Html on Boris van Katwijk</title>
    <link>https://bvkatwijk.github.io/tags/html/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Html on Boris van Katwijk</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 11:03:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://bvkatwijk.github.io/tags/html/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ads on your Blog site</title>
      <link>https://bvkatwijk.github.io/blog/google-adsense/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 09:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bvkatwijk.github.io/blog/google-adsense/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For a side project I had to add some advertisements, and while I was at it, I also added Google Ads onto my blog. Not so much as to make money (I don&amp;rsquo;t expect a lot of traffic here) but to learn how to do it in various environments. It can be a very useful skill if you are running a free website to cover hosting or if you want to provide this as a service to others.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combining htmx with Bootstrap</title>
      <link>https://bvkatwijk.github.io/blog/htmx-and-bootstrap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 10:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bvkatwijk.github.io/blog/htmx-and-bootstrap/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Using &lt;a href=&#34;http://htmx.org/&#34;&gt;htmx&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href=&#34;https://getbootstrap.com/&#34;&gt;Bootstrap&lt;/a&gt; is mostly a seamless experience, but I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered a few places where a bit of extra effort is needed to smooth everything out. Since I could not find a concise description of the required fix, I&amp;rsquo;ve created this quick post to outline the issue and the remedy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;bootstrap&#34;&gt;Bootstrap&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since I work mostly on business-to-business administrative web applications, I need to build many interfaces, yet a slick or custom styling is usually not the highest priority. We need a well rounded set of standard component that enables data presentation with clarity.&#xA;So let&amp;rsquo;s just pretend we still live in the &amp;rsquo;10s and use &lt;a href=&#34;https://getbootstrap.com/&#34;&gt;Bootstrap&lt;/a&gt;. A benefit is that all the scraping-trained AI&amp;rsquo;s are now all Bootstrap experts, meaning that stamping out entire dashboards is trivial.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>j2html</title>
      <link>https://bvkatwijk.github.io/blog/j2html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 10:33:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bvkatwijk.github.io/blog/j2html/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For my full-stack projects I like to use Server-Side rendering with &lt;a href=&#34;https://javalin.io/&#34;&gt;Javalin&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://j2html.com/&#34;&gt;j2html&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://htmx.org/&#34;&gt;htmx&lt;/a&gt;. Together, these libraries allow you to write interactive full-stack web applications in vanilla java. In this post I&amp;rsquo;d like to explain how the &lt;a href=&#34;https://j2html.com/&#34;&gt;j2html&lt;/a&gt; library fits in this setup, go over a few benefits, and link a &lt;a href=&#34;https://bvankatwijk.nl/j2html-converter/&#34;&gt;converter&lt;/a&gt; that I wrote to make building the user interface easier.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;server-side-rendering&#34;&gt;Server Side Rendering&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While the last decade was dominated by client-side frameworks, many applications could perhaps have saved a lot of development time by using server-side rendering. This means that the resulting html is built on the server, including its data, styling and behaviour.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Link Swapping</title>
      <link>https://bvkatwijk.github.io/blog/security---link-swapping/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 09:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bvkatwijk.github.io/blog/security---link-swapping/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re on a website and you see a link, how do you figure out where that link will take you? Just hover over it right? Try to hovering this &lt;a href = &#34;https://wikipedia.org&#34; onclick=&#34;this.href = &#39;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dQw4w9WgXcQ&#39;;&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Totally Legitimate Link&lt;/a&gt;. If you dare, click it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve clicked the link, welcome back! Refresh the page to have the link in it&amp;rsquo;s initial state again. Not everything is what it seems, and this is also very true when browsing the web.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
